I spring fans welcome to another
我春天的歌迷欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装弹簧提示
week's installment we're going to again
本周的分期付款，我们将再次
revisit our socket now in a previous
现在在以前的版本中重新访问我们的套接字
installment of spring tips without the
没有安装弹簧头的安装
our socket we're in I introduced the the
我们在我们的插座，我介绍了
protocol our socket and the client-side
协议我们的套接字和客户端
library developed by Facebook in built
Facebook开发的内置库
upon reactor right and so in that video
在反应堆右边，在那个视频中
we looked at let's say raw our socket
我们看着我们说原始的插座
right just a low-level or socket and III
只是一个低级或套接字而已
foreshadowed the idea that that one day
预示着这一天的想法
when one sweet day we'd have a support
当一个甜蜜的日子，我们会得到支持
for our socket in the spring framework
在Spring框架中用于我们的插座
itself for that day has come at long
那天本身已经很久了
last my friends and so what I want to
最后我的朋友，所以我想
talk to you about today is how to use
跟你说说今天是如何使用
our socket with spring and to look at
我们带弹簧的插座，看看
what are the opportunities here now a
现在这里有什么机会
quick revision I think is in order our
我认为是为了快速修订
socket at the end of the day is a
一天结束时的插座是
protocol it's a cross-platform language
协议，它是一种跨平台的语言
agnostic protocol that was designed by
设计的不可知协议
Facebook with input and design from
来自Facebook的意见和设计
people who came over from Netflix on how
来自Netflix的人们如何
to build highly available micro service
建立高可用性的微服务
centric systems and the goal here was to
中心系统，这里的目标是
provide an application protocol an
提供一个应用协议
application use case centric protocol
以应用程序用例为中心的协议
right as opposed to HTTP which you might
与HTTP相反，您可能会
differentiate and call for example a
区分并称呼例如
document retrieval protocol these use
这些使用的文档检索协议
cases are orthogonal the one I think
情况是正交的，我认为
complements the other but they are not
补充对方，但不是
the same thing and so it's for this
同样的事情，为此
reason that this protocol was necessary
该协议必要的原因
there are a number of different
有很多不同的
limitations with with with HTTP that
HTTP的局限性
just don't make it a great fit for
只是不适合
homogeneous communication obviously the
同类交流显然
biggest single differentiating feature
最大的单一差异化特征
is the interoperability that it extends
是它扩展的互操作性
to people who are using the open web and
给使用开放网络的人，
that's not to be ignored and of course
这是不容忽视的，当然
don't sleep on that particular feature
不要睡在那个特殊的功能上
but if you want to if you wanted to
但是如果你想的话
support some of the more common message
支持一些更常见的消息
exchange patterns for example request
交换模式，例如请求
response that's pretty natural to do
很自然地做出回应
with HTTP but what about a
与HTTP，但怎么样
fire-and-forget right how do you sit how
开火忘了，你怎么坐
do you send a message and then ignore
你发送消息然后忽略
the response and and get the performance
响应并获得表现
optimizations on both producer and
生产者和生产者的优化
consumer associate with that exchange
与该交易所建立联系的消费者
what about requesting a or sending a
关于请求一个或发送一个
value and then getting a stream of
价值，然后得到
values back and unending stream
值回无止境
this is certainly possible with service
服务一定可以做到
and events but source service and events
和事件，但源服务和事件
as well as um
以及嗯
WebSockets they don't have headers all
他们没有头的WebSockets
right there's no way to for a stream
没办法流
level sort of message
级别的消息
there's no way to perpetuate a token for
没有办法永久保留令牌
example so this news case is one that's
例子，所以这个新闻案例是
just not well served this is one use
只是服务不好这是一种用途
case that's just not well served in our
这种情况在我们的服务中得不到很好的解决
application and in the protocol itself
应用程序以及协议本身
in the platform another thing that's a
在平台上另一件事是
sort of you interesting is what about
有点有趣的是什么
bi-directional streaming like how do I
双向流式
do you know ongoing communication again
你知道继续沟通吗
you can use WebSockets for that but
您可以为此使用WebSockets
again that makes that it has some
再次使它有一些
limitations and it certainly doesn't
局限性，当然不是
solve the sort of question of how do I
解决我该怎么办的问题
have something that's initiated by the
有一些由
server right why does it have to be the
服务器正确，为什么它必须是
consumer that makes a request and then
发出请求的消费者，然后
initiates the discussion why can't it be
发起讨论，为什么不能
the other way around and so this for
反之亦然
this use case we you know we need
这个用例，我们知道我们需要
something a bit more sophisticated when
有点复杂
I say sophisticated I don't mean
我说我不是故意的
something new right we've already had
我们已经拥有的一些新权利
we've already got TCP we've already got
我们已经有了TCP我们已经有了
this mechanism there so that allows that
这种机制在那里，使
it's just a little low-level and it's
这只是一个低级的
fairly easy to shoot yourself in the
很容易在
foot with that low-level sort of uh you
脚跟那种低水平的你
know transport so that's one thing
懂运输，那是一回事
another thing is the our Saka is
另一件事是我们的坂
agnostic of payload it doesn't matter
与有效载荷无关的无关紧要
what you want to send across the wire
您想通过电线发送什么
it's binary data and you can conduct
它是二进制数据，您可以进行
yourself even connect anything you like
你自己甚至可以连接任何你喜欢的东西
across that then that transport it could
跨越那个运输它可以
be a JSON string it could be binary
是JSON字符串，可能是二进制
streams of video or data or whatever but
视频或数据流或其他
it's up to you right so with HTTP how do
这取决于您，因此使用HTTP怎么做
you send an image while you base64
您在base64上发送图像
base64 encode the binary data and then
base64编码二进制数据，然后
on the other side you on base64 encode
另一方面，您使用base64编码
it and you read it in into binary data
它，然后将其读入二进制数据
this is despite the fact that ultimately
尽管事实上，最终
HTTP is you know behind the scenes
HTTP是您的幕后知识吗
there's binary right so you go to you go
有二进制的权利，所以你去吧
from binary to the textual
从二进制到文本
representation that HTTP requires which
HTTP需要哪个表示
then get to the base64 thing then you go
然后进入base64的事情，然后你去
back to binary and it's just super
回到二进制，它超级好
inefficient so you know these are just
效率低下，所以您知道这些只是
sort of things that we want another
我们想要另一种东西
thing at our sake
为了我们
gives you is a built-in frame in the
给你一个内置的框架
protocol proper that allows you to
适当的协议，使您能够
communicate availability right that is
传达可用性权利
to say the client can ask the producer
说客户可以问生产者
the consumer can ask the producer how
消费者可以问生产者
much uptime do you have what is your
你有多少正常运行时间
health right
健康权
with spring we've got the spring boot we
春天，我们有了春天的靴子
have the actuator module and that module
有执行器模块和那个模块
hangs off the side of your a web
悬挂在您的网络一侧
application off of JMX or HTTP and it
JMX或HTTP及其它的应用程序
communicates just that kind of
交流那种
information that out of band
带外信息
availability information right that out
可用性信息就可以了
of band health information metrics
频段健康信息指标
things like that things that the client
像客户那样的事情
if it knows about it can look to to sort
如果知道的话可以去排序
of decide whether it should rewrite
决定是否应该重写
itself to another note right or some
本身对另一个音符或一些
sort of intermediary infrastructure can
某种中介基础设施可以
also decide whether that service is sick
还要确定服务是否生病
well this is something that has to be
好吧，这是必须要做的
arranged right it's an agreement between
安排正确，这是之间的协议
the spring boot convention of having the
春季启动惯例
actuator and the engineers and the
执行器和工程师以及
infrastructure etc well now that problem
基础设施等等现在这个问题
goes away and now it's built into the
消失了，现在已经内置到
protocol proper there's every
正确的协议
expectation that you will want to ask
期望你会问
this question and have an answer so we
这个问题，并有一个答案，所以我们
get a lot of benefits by using our
通过使用我们的服务获得很多好处
socket um our socket doesn't have a few
套接字，我们的套接字没有几个
things right if you're using regular
如果您使用常规的话就没事了
low-level our socket as I introduced in
我介绍的底层套接字
that first video you'll notice that
在第一个视频中，您会注意到
there is no for example no support for
例如，不支持
routing right what does it mean to route
正确的路由是什么意思
well when a client connects to a port
客户端连接到端口时很好
you have an open connection and that's
你有一个开放的连接，那就是
it you know what you you know how do you
你知道你知道你怎么做
divide the logic how do you divide the
划分逻辑你如何划分
business logic into different handlers
将业务逻辑放入不同的处理程序中
with the HTTP and spring it's very
使用HTTP和spring的时候
common to say ok I've got a handler that
通常说好吧，我有一个处理程序，
lives at a certain path the URI and that
生活在URI的某个路径上
that helps the web framework these
这些可以帮助网络框架
determine what component to invoke in
确定要调用的组件
response right well there is no obvious
反应很好，没有明显的反应
sort of support for that out of the box
开箱即用的支持
with the protocol proper but spring and
与适当的协议，但春天和
our new messaging model provides that
我们的新消息传递模型提供了
the message mapping annotation rather
消息映射注释，而不是
provides that another thing that there's
提供了另一件事
no support for out of the box because
不支持开箱即用
it's agnostic to this particular use
它与这种特殊用途无关
case is how do you converge how do you
情况是如何融合的
conduct payloads how do you send a you
进行有效载荷你如何发送你
know bytes from point A to point B right
知道从A点到B点的字节
in our socket you send anything you want
在我们的套接字中，您可以发送任何想要的信息
and there's no way to sort of figure out
而且没有办法弄清楚
what the content is you have to kind of
您必须要提供什么内容
encode
编码
in the headers what you can do but we do
在标题中，您可以做什么，但我们可以
that for you we can do message
为您，我们可以做消息
conversion in the spring our socket
在春季转换我们的插座
supports so let's take a look at that
支持，让我们来看看
now that we've kind of got a feel for
现在，我们对
what is there and what isn't there and
那里有什么不在那里
we got a feel for what's possible let's
我们对可能的感觉，让我们
go ahead and build a new application as
继续构建一个新的应用程序
always using my second favorite place in
总是用我第二个最喜欢的地方
the internet start that spring that IO
互联网从那个春天开始
I'm going to use spring boot to that oh
我要用弹簧靴哦
sorry 2.20 snapshot and we to build the
对不起2.20快照，我们来建立
two modules producer and consumer I'm
我是两个模块的生产者和消费者
gonna use the are socket support that
将使用are socket支持
checkbox by the by only works in the
by的复选框仅在
latest in greatest I suspect it will be
我怀疑这是最新的
available for 2.0 to tattoo now m2 but
现在可用于纹身2.0平方米，但
for now I'm just gonna constrain myself
现在我只是要约束自己
to 2.2 snapshot because it's it's there
到2.2快照，因为它在那里
for that it's not there for two two and
因为它不存在两个两个
one
一
okay so I'm gonna use reactive web as
好的，所以我要使用反应式网页
well let's see and that's it that should
好吧，让我们看看，就是这样
be enough for us to to have everything
足以让我们拥有一切
we need I'll bring in dev tools and
我们需要引入开发工具，
that's the producer hit generate will do
那是制作人命中将产生的
consumer hit generate alright and now
消费者的打击产生了好，现在
you a Oh producer
你是哦制作人
all right and now we have our consumer
好的，现在我们有我们的消费者
that's over here so ueo consumer and
就在这里，所以消费者和
we're gonna keep the producer on the
我们要让制片人继续
left and the consumer on the right on
左，消费者在右
the producer side we're just gonna build
我们将要建立的生产方
a our socket service there's no HTTP
我们的套接字服务没有HTTP
involved so I'm gonna go ahead and
参与其中，所以我要继续前进，
comment out this bit right here and
在这里评论一下，
there we go okay so now we've got two
那里我们可以，所以现在我们有两个
sides to applications let's close this
应用程序方面，让我们结束这一点
out here's the producer and here's the
在这里是生产者，这是
consumer we're just gonna develop these
消费者，我们将开发这些
things in tandem now the auto
串联的东西现在自动
configuration for swing boot will setup
Swing Boot的配置将安装
the producer side we'll set up a our
生产者方面，我们将建立一个
socket server for us assuming I specify
假设我指定了我们的套接字服务器
a port so our socket port equals that
一个端口，因此我们的套接字端口等于
say 7,000 and I'll do a lazy
说7,000，我会偷懒
initialization great and there we go so
初始化很棒，我们就这样
there's our our socket server we can
这是我们的套接字服务器，我们可以
start that up on the consumer side I'm
从消费者方面开始
gonna use an our socket request turn the
将使用我们的套接字请求打开
auto the auto configuration doesn't
自动自动配置不
provide that for us but you know it
为我们提供，但您知道
provides most of what we need until we
提供我们所需的大部分，直到我们
can just depend on that so I'm going to
可以依靠它，所以我要
pay that here I'm gonna create an our
付钱，我要在这里创建我们的
socket connection and this is again
套接字连接，这又是
fairly you know this should be familiar
相当，你知道这应该很熟悉
if you watch that first video so I
如果你看第一个视频，那么我
cannot stress enough how much you should
无法承受足够的压力
watch that so TCP client transport and
注意，这样TCP客户端传输和
start block data dam data frame they did
他们做的起跑数据坝数据帧
a mime type that'll be mime type utils
一个将成为mime type utils的mime类型
application Jason utf-8 and we want
应用程序Jason utf-8，我们想要
transport we were to get that what else
运输我们要得到什么
do we need what else do we need frame
我们需要其他什么我们需要框架吗
decoder payload decoder 0 copy and
解码器有效负载解码器0复制并
that's that and I'm gonna use a our
就是这样，我要使用我们的
socket requester this is like the web
套接字请求者，这就像网络
client from spring web flex our socket
来自spring web的客户可以灵活地使用我们的套接字
requester okay
请求者还可以
I'm gonna inject the our socket
我要注入我们的插座
reference and I'm gonna use my type
参考，我将使用我的类型
utils application adjacent value and
utils应用程序的相邻值和
then finally we need the our socket
然后最后我们需要我们的插座
strategies object that Springs Auto
Springs Auto的策略对象
configuration welcome what will
配置欢迎会
automatically equate for us okay so
自动等同于我们好吧，所以
let's put that in there
让我们放在那里
this doesn't need to be a value it needs
这不必是它需要的值
to be the actual you know object okay
成为实际的你知道的对象好吗
good so we've got all that now in one
好，所以我们现在就将所有这些
place we can build a client that will
我们可以建立一个可以
talk to our service and our service is
谈论我们的服务，我们的服务是
just a regular controller I'm gonna call
只是我要打电话给的常规控制器
this the greetings our socket our saw
这是我们的问候，我们看到了
get controller okay I'm gonna have an
得到控制器好，我要去
entity of type class greetings
类型问候类的实体
request class readings response okay and
请求班级阅读答案好
our request will have a name that we're
我们的请求将使用一个
going to greet and this will have a
要打招呼，这将有一个
greeting okay very very simple now I
问候好吧，现在非常非常简单，我
want to data at all ours
想要记录我们所有的数据
no args good add these compile-time
没有args好加上这些编译时间
annotations good now here we're going to
注释很好，现在我们要
create a builder here so it'll be
在这里创建一个构建器，它将
readings request with reading ok string
带有确定字符串的读数请求
message turn this after I do this dot
我做完这个点后，消息变成这个
sorry I want this in the response don't
对不起，我希望在响应中不要这样做
on greetings response here we go good
在问候回应这里我们很好
stuff so this step greeting equals
东西，所以这一步问候等于
message credit constructor here for the
此处的消息信用构造函数
common case which is one that you know
你知道的一种常见情况
we'll see it'll take a name and I'll
我们会看到它的名字，我会
produce a response for us so we'll say
对我们产生回应，所以我们说
this dot with reading hello name at
这个点，上面有你好名字
instant dot now alright this is a
即时点现在好了，这是一个
response good stuff okay so if you give
反应好东西好吧，如果你给
us a name we'll create a default thing
给我们起个名字，我们将创建一个默认的东西
for you if not we'll just you can use
如果没有，我们会为您服务
the Builder ok so there's no argument
建造者好，所以没有争论
version that as well
那个版本
so there we go we got that now um I've
所以我们走了，我们现在知道了
got a I've got a a billet of create a
我有一个创建的方坯
response quickly I've got the pail the
迅速反应，我得到了
carrier of the detail for the request
请求细节的载体
which has a name now I'm gonna copy and
现在我要复制一个名字
paste that for easy interoperation
粘贴以方便互操作
to the other side to the producer and
到生产者的另一边
the consumer so now both have the same
消费者，所以现在两者都相同
types obviously you would need to you
类型显然你需要
know extricate that somehow I started
知道我以某种方式开始
with mutual shared library or something
与共同共享的图书馆或其他东西
like that or not right again this you
喜欢还是不喜欢这个你
can just create your own clients and
可以创建自己的客户，
representations if it's trivial enough
表示是否足够琐碎
who cares so now we've got the the types
谁在乎，所以现在我们有了类型
let's create our controller here okay
让我们在这里创建控制器吧
and the controller is gonna have let's
控制器将让我们
demonstrate the absolute simplest thing
展示绝对最简单的东西
that could possibly work first
可能首先工作
so message mapping greet okay and all
所以消息映射好了，所有
we're gonna do is we're gonna return a
我们要做的是我们将返回一个
single string sorry not a string and
单字符串，抱歉不是字符串，并且
greetings response given a request that
问候响应给出了以下要求
is of type greetings request okay and
是类型的问候请求还可以，
new greetings response okay and it'll be
新的问候响应好吧，它将是
a request get name that's the absolute
请求获取名称是绝对的
simplest one that could work and that
最简单的可行的
you can see that this is not a path per
您可以看到这不是
se like I said the routing is now
就像我说的路由现在
something that spring provides we're
春天提供的东西
saying this string this label greet maps
说这个标签迎接地图的字符串
to this logic if you want to invoke that
如果要调用该逻辑
something has to communicate that that
必须传达一些信息
string in a way that will be understood
字符串以一种可以理解的方式
and they are the are our socket
它们是我们的插座
requester will do that for you so what
请求者将为您做到这一点，那又如何
I'm gonna do here is I'm gonna create a
我要在这里做，我要创建一个
client that is actually just a rest
客户实际上只是休息
controller so we can actually invoke
控制器，因此我们可以实际调用
them in the browser and see the results
在浏览器中查看结果
okay so greetings rest controller
好的，所以问候休息控制器
alright and this will have an endpoint
好了，这会有一个终点
called greet and we'll say publisher of
叫做greet，我们会说
what greetings response greet path
什么问候回应打招呼
variable string name I'm gonna say this
可变的字符串名称，我要说这个
dot greet as hi this dot we need a
点打招呼，因为这个点，我们需要一个
requester now write requester add that
请求者现在写请求者添加
to the constructor this dot requester
给构造函数这个点请求者
dot route and it's just gonna meet greet
点路线，只是会见面
and when send some data the data is
当发送一些数据时，数据是
gonna be a new footings request right
会成为新的立足点
new greetings request and the request
新的问候请求和请求
will have a name which is going to pass
将具有将要通过的名称
in there we're expecting a response back
在那儿，我们期待得到回应
in this case it's just a single value so
在这种情况下，它只是一个值，所以
we'll expect a mano of type greetings
我们会期待问候类型
response okay let me turn that so now
回应好吧，现在让我转一下
we've restarted the we've got the
我们已经重启了
service let's just make sure I've
服务让我们确保我已经
restarted that I'm not sure when I read
重新启动，我不确定何时阅读
last day we started it okay and then
昨天我们开始了，然后
here we'll restart this so now on the
在这里，我们将重新启动它，所以现在在
client-side running on port 8080 you can
客户端可以在端口8080上运行
see I've got the web server on port 8080
看到端口8080上有Web服务器
I don't have the web server over here
我这里没有网络服务器
looks like I got rid of the web flow web
看起来我摆脱了网络流网络
plugs divinity
塞神
I do have Nitti our socket started on
我确实有Nitti，我们的插座开始了
the other side I don't have MIDI our
另一面我没有MIDI我们
socket because I didn't specify a port
套接字，因为我没有指定端口
so the consumer the auto configuration
所以消费者自动配置
kicks in but it does everything except
踢进去，但除了能做所有的事
for start the the web server the our
用于启动Web服务器
socket server which is good because I
套接字服务器，这很好，因为我
might I might want to for example um use
我可能想例如使用
the configuration but set up the
配置，但设置
transport to be the web socket support
传输为Web套接字支持
provided from our spring web flex engine
由我们的spring web flex引擎提供
for example so you can actually do our
例如，这样您就可以实际执行
socket over WebSockets for example and
例如，通过WebSockets进行套接字和
spring the spring boot auto
春天春天引导自动
configuration can wire that up for you
配置可以为您服务
if you like but the point is you know
如果你喜欢，但重点是你知道
you have to kind of opt into these
您必须选择加入这些
different features and if you're in this
不同的功能，如果你在这个
case all I want is to act as a client so
我想做的就是代理客户
for example I want the our socket
例如我想要我们的插座
strategies to get work wired up for me
为我整理工作的策略
and I need a client our socket reference
我需要一个客户我们的套接字参考
but other than that everything is
但除此之外，一切都是
already provided for me okay
已经为我提供了
all right let's see so we go to
好吧，让我们看看，我们去
localhost greet world all right and I
本地主机欢迎世界，我
didn't provide a name today where's my
今天没有提供名字我的名字在哪里
oh right greet
哦，打招呼
name restart
重新启动名称
okay there's my greeting as I increment
好吧，随着我的增加我在问候
is a refresh the browser you see the
是刷新浏览器，您看到
timestamp increasing ever upward okay
时间戳不断增加可以
alright so that's in and out that's just
好吧，那进进出出只是
one value in one value out behind the
一值一值
scenes these values are being sent
这些值正在发送的场景
around as payloads well of course you
周围当然是有效载荷
can do streaming as well so for example
也可以进行流式传输，例如
let's say I want to have an endpoint
假设我想要一个端点
that was a service an endpoint endpoints
那是端点服务
of produces media type right type dot
产生媒体类型右类型点
text event stream value is weet SS e
文本事件流的值为weet SS e
name
名称
alright so publisher of reading response
好的，所以阅读反应的发布者
path variable string name here we're
路径变量字符串名称在这里
going to use this thing to bleeped you
要用这个东西让你流血
know streamed okay I'm gonna call the
知道流媒体好吧，我要打电话给
greet stream endpoint and the data we're
迎接流端点和我们的数据
gonna send as before is this when we get
当我们得到时，将像以前一样发送
back that ok so just replace alright so
回来，好吧，所以就换个好吧
retrieve in this case a flux of
在这种情况下检索
responses and so I'm calling the our
回应，所以我称我们的
socket end point using the our socket
使用我们的插座的插座终点
requester we know that it's pointing to
请求者，我们知道它指向
point to port 7000 because that's what
指向端口7000，因为那是
we specified there now on the server
我们现在在服务器上指定了
side I need to actually provide this
我需要实际提供
endpoint the greet stream endpoint so
终结问候流终结点
I'll do that I'll say at message mapping
我会在邮件映射中说
flux of greetings response weed stream
问候反应流杂草流
greet request and our job is to say flux
迎接要求，我们的工作是说助焊剂
dot from stream stream generate news of
流中的点生成新闻
the fire and then delay elements
起火，然后延迟元素
duration of seconds when to gonna
几秒钟的持续时间
stagger the results you see me do that
错开结果，你看到我这样做
when I introduced a service and events
当我介绍一项服务和事件时
for example so new greetings response
例如，新的问候回应
and then the name will get from the
然后名称将从
request so as before this is that now
要求，就像现在这样
we're gonna iterate
我们要迭代
and you know will provide many values
而且您会提供很多价值
that'll have incrementing time stamps
时间戳会增加
alright so same thing greet stream greet
好吧，同样的事情打招呼，流打招呼
stream I'm gonna send back a publisher
流，我要发回发布者
of greetings response whose results will
的问候回应，其结果将
be staggered every one second we'll get
每隔一秒钟就会被错开
a new one okay okay now we go here to we
一个新的，好吧，好吧，现在我们去这里
stream before did I say I said SSE world
流之前我说过我说过SSE世界
there you go
你去
so we're streaming data right we're
所以我们正在流式传输数据
actually streaming data over the network
通过网络实际流式传输数据
here not using HTTP or anything like
这里不使用HTTP或类似的东西
that where's the Gateway where we have a
那是我们有一个网关的地方
node that is the consumer it's got a
作为消费者的节点，它有一个
client and the user interface is the
客户端和用户界面是
HTTP API but the actual logic the actual
HTTP API但实际逻辑实际
data is being streamed from the other
数据正在从另一个流式传输
our socket server and we're getting it
我们的套接字服务器，我们得到了它
and it's just it's reactive back all the
只是它是反应性的
way through so I get all these nice
通过所有这些很好的方式
operators and I can use back pressure
操作员和我可以使用背压
and I can do all that um this is I think
我可以做所有这件事，我认为
a really nice sort of arrangement right
非常好的安排
you can actually do some very
你实际上可以做一些非常
interesting things and this is not more
有趣的事情，这不是更多
difficult to express than the HTTP stuff
比HTTP东西更难表达
quite quite the contrary it's actually
事实恰恰相反
easier um and you have some you know
容易一些，你知道一些
it's it's spring so we have for example
是春天，所以我们有
for a handle errors you have a nice way
对于句柄错误，您有一个不错的方法
to do that you can say okay well let's
为此，您可以说好吧，让我们
say I wanted to return a publisher of
说我想退还的出版商
greetings responses error handler given
给定的问候响应错误处理程序
a legal argument exception I a okay so
法律论据例外，我可以，所以
flux dot just new
助焊剂点刚刚
greetings response dot with greeting Oh
问候回应点与问候哦
No
没有
so if something goes wrong if a if a
所以如果出问题了
endpoint throws an illegal argument
端点引发非法论点
exception for whatever reason then this
出于某种原因的例外，那么这
will get called and I'll have a chance
会打电话给我，我有机会
to provide the response to default the
提供对默认值的响应
response that I want rather than rather
我想要而不是宁愿回应
than having a bubble back up to the user
而不是向用户返回气泡
and so let's create that endpoint here
所以我们在这里创建该端点
message
信息
mapping error okay it'll be a flux of
映射错误好吧，这将是
reading response error and all I'm gonna
阅读响应错误，我要做的就是
do then they say return mono that error
然后他们说返回单声道错误
new legal
新法律
arguments oh oh it's gonna be a flux
论点哦，那会变的
touch error there you go okay so that's
触摸错误，你可以，所以那是
my error endpoint on the client-side
我在客户端的错误端点
we'll just create an endpoint that we
我们将创建一个端点
can call
可以打电话
so error publisher greeting response and
因此错误的发布者问候响应和
we'll start this of course on this side
我们当然会从这边开始
we'll say error and this dot requester
我们会说错误和这个点请求者
dot route error dot retrieve want to
点路径错误点检索想要
send nothing in the payload so it'll
在有效负载中不发送任何内容，因此它将
just be mono dot empty I guess and then
只是单点空我猜然后
retrieve whatever right we don't care
检索任何我们不在乎的权利
greeting response dot class and then we
问候响应点类，然后我们
can restart the server and then the
可以重新启动服务器，然后
browser go to air and it says oh no so
浏览器转播，它说哦不
we actually got the default fallback
我们实际上得到了默认的后备
value that we wanted right that's
我们想要正确的价值是
actually very useful so so now we've got
实际上非常有用，所以现在我们有了
our socket we've got we've seen how we
我们的插座，我们已经看到了我们如何
can use the message mapping facilities
可以使用消息映射功能
in in Spring Framework 5.2 and spring
在Spring Framework 5.2和spring中
boot 2.2 we've looked at how to expose
启动2.2，我们研究了如何公开
endpoints using the message mapping
端点使用消息映射
annotations these are fairly familiar if
这些注解相当熟悉，如果
you've ever used the web socket support
您曾经使用过Web套接字支持
in spring um there's still some more
在春天，还有更多
work to be done and you know things are
要完成的工作，你知道事情是
exciting I I'm excited to see this land
激动，我很高兴看到这片土地
and spring framework already and work
和Spring框架已经可以工作
has already been afoot and his is
已经走了，他的是
surging ahead on supporting our socket
急于支持我们的插座
and spring cloud gateway so the our
和Spring Cloud Gateway，因此我们的
socket support in Spring cog gateway
Spring Cog网关中的套接字支持
well I mean you can imagine some of the
好吧，我的意思是你可以想象一些
possibilities here you can imagine for
您可以想象这里的可能性
example having a server that's
拥有一台服务器的示例
completely locked down it's a black box
完全锁定它是一个黑匣子
and then it initiates a connection to
然后启动与
the Gateway because you can have
网关，因为您可以拥有
stateful long live connections that do
有状态的万岁连接
duplex kind of communication that that
那种双向通讯
gateway can maintain open connections
网关可以保持开放连接
from each of the micro services which
从每个微服务中
reach out to the gate Erol right so the
伸向Erol门，所以
Gateway isn't connecting to the micro
网关未连接到微型
service
服务
it's either way around and there's no
无论哪种方式都没有
ingress into those micro services so
进入那些微服务，所以
they're imminently secure and then they
他们迫在眉睫，然后他们
have the ability to in
有能力
the Gateway could for example be the the
网关可以是例如
router it could say oh well I have this
路由器可能会说哦，我有这个
this connection to this micro Service
与此微服务的连接
open I asked it it has enough capacity
打开我问它有足够的容量
enough availability and up enough of
足够的可用性和足够的
time enough health whatever so I'm gonna
有足够的时间健康，我该怎么办
route the request to it right so it can
将请求正确路由到它，以便可以
do that I mean it has ability to ask
我是说它有能力问
that question and then seamlessly you
这个问题，然后无缝地你
know move streams from one node to
知道将流从一个节点移到
another right so lots of really
另一个权利真的很多
interesting possibilities here the the
有趣的可能性在这里
best is yet to come as always but I hope
最好的事情还是一如既往，但我希望
you give this stuff a try feedback and
你给这个东西一个尝试反馈，
let us know so without my friends thanks
让我知道，不用我的朋友谢谢
for watching and as always we'll see you
观看，一如既往，我们会见到你
next
下一个
you
您